horsetopia.com 2003-12-06

# Horsetopia.com Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy for Horse-for-Sale.org in conjunction with Horsetopia.com

#### Your Email Address

We will not sell, rent, or give your email address to anyone. You will never receive junk mail as a result of filling out forms on Horse-for-Sale.org. Also, when we create your webpage, we will hide your email address so that only serious buyers will reach you, and you never have to give out your email address if you do not want to. Since we are an advertiser rather than an intermediary, we have no part in your dealings with potential buyers, so what you may disclose at that point is at your discretion. 

#### Your other personal information

All of the above info also applies to the rest of your personal information. We will protect all of your personal information to the best of our ability, and will never sell or give your information to anyone. Note that upon signup, you will have the option of what personal contact information to include on your website (name, phone number, etc.). 

#### Cookies

Cookies are small bits of information stored on your computer. We use cookies to verify that you have properly logged in if you try to edit your listing, and to remember your login info if you check the box marked "Remember my login info" when logging in. We do not store or access any personal information at all through cookies. You can turn cookies off in Netscape using "Edit... Preferences...Advanced" or in Internet Explorer with "Tools...Internet Options". 

#### Other Concerns

Our concern for your privacy is indicated by the specifics above. In short, we don't give away or sell any personal information. If you have a question about any other issues not addressed, please don't hesitate to contact us at [support@horse-for-sale.org](mailto:support@horse-for-sale.org).
